Special guest in our studio, Zal is back. Welcome back, Zal.
Thank you for having me on again, Paul and Mike. It's an absolute pleasure to be here.
Zalstock is coming.
Yeah, I love his, he's got a hoodie on. Zalstock 26.
Yes, and I goofed earlier when I said tomorrow. For some reason, I keep thinking today is Friday.
Well, you had Monday off. Your whole week is thrown off.
But the event is coming up Saturday, and it's going to be awesome. A day full of live music.
Tell us a little bit about it.
And what a big thing, because I remember you and I got together early in the summer to start talking about this.
Maybe it was in late spring, and here we are.
Yeah, a couple days out. We're really excited.
We're part of the ninth annual Art of Ellsworth Main Craft Fair weekend, Zalstock Music Fest.
It's going to be an opportunity for me to bring my digital community here locally,
and both be able to present to my local community and also my digital community what each have to offer.
So it's going to be an absolute blast.
So we're going to have eight amazing acts, and it's going to be a free event all day starting at 12 to 6 p.m.
Wow.
And then at 6 p.m., things move inside to the Black Moon Public House?
Exactly.
We're going to be having an after party with our partners at Black Moon,
going inside and having an awesome opportunity to have some more music from an amazing organization organized by Steve and the Black Moon community.
So we're going to be having a blast with them right after.
So if you're having fun with us, you can move on inside and keep the party going.
Well, you've got a lot of experience in putting music festivals together.
Has this been a tricky one for you, or has it been easy?
You know, it's actually been a lot of fun.
It's been really easy because the community here in Maine has been so receptive and supportive on the journey.
Whomever I'm talking to, whether it be through cold emails or in person,
has been unbelievably helpful in, even if they can't directly support us, directing us to someone who can.
So that's been an absolute blast, and that's actually how I met you guys here.
Yeah.
Yeah, this is all.
Yeah, I met Zal.
Zal has a Zal.
I met him at a business after hours.
It was in the springtime.
And then we just started talking, and here we are.
So this is exciting.
And in a few minutes, we're going to go through the timeline.
Zal is going to tell us the bands and just what to expect on Saturday.
All right.
More with Zal coming up.
We're talking Zal Stock, the music festival that will take place in downtown Ellsworth this Saturday beginning at 12 noon.
More next on Star 97.7.
This weekend, Maine Craft weekend.
It's going to be a busy and fun time in downtown Ellsworth.
And Zal has the live music covered with Zal Stock, a music festival that will begin at the Franklin Street Parklet at noon on Saturday.
Somebody said better call Zal.
So we did.
And he's with us now.
He's here.
So what can people expect, Zal?
I mean, who's going to be performing and when?
Yeah, we got eight amazing acts.
So we're going to be starting right at noon with the Crown Vicks, a rock and roll dance band.
So that's going to be an amazing start.
And we're going to be going right in with our three bands to start.
Our second band is going to be Open X, a power pop rock band.
And Grass Rug, an indie jam rock band.
So that's going to be our first three acts, starting us off with three bands.
And then we're going to be getting into some of our solo acts.
So we have Acadia Rising with World Rhythms and Michael Anderson as a solo pianist.
And that's going to be rounding out our five main musicians.
And then we're going to be getting into some of our musicians from over around the U.S.
D. Coop, Lions Den, and Tom Fellenz.
So D. Coop had an amazing opportunity to help me organize a community event earlier this year in the DMV area where he lives.
Lions Den, Rez Music is a musician that I met down there that D. Coop had performing and have the amazing opportunity of after seeing him perform there, see that he'd be a perfect fit for Maine and brought him up here.
And then we have rounding us off Tom Fellenz, who's an unbelievable musician in so many different ways and has helped organize our event and is going to be live streaming it out to our audience as well.
So really excited to have these eight acts of different kinds of music and lots of different themes.
So whether you're into one genre or another, there'll be something for you from 12 to 6 at the Franklin Street Parklet.
Wow. And it's all free.
Exactly. All free.
And I see on your website, too, that there's a tab for volunteer.
Are you looking for volunteers?
Yeah, one million percent.
So we're always looking for volunteers.
That's how we make our free events work.
We have people from all over the globe that are actually supporting this event in different capacities, whether they can make it here or not.
So if you want to sign up as a volunteer, we're always looking for more volunteers.
And we're actually going to be starting our local push for after this event for Zao Ellsworth.
So we're going to be meeting in person weekly and starting to help organize our local community here for hopefully the next Zao Fest.
Wow. That is awesome.
It is free to attend.
No ticket, no gate.
But you can support the eight artists who are playing, and you can do that in person and also at zaostock.com.
That's Z-A-O-Stock.com.
Really cool to have you here.
The weather should be fantastic, Zoll, on Saturday.
And I'm sure you're going to have an awesome Zao Stock.
A million percent.
I just want to say thank you to you guys, Star 97.7, one of our partners, as well as a lot of other partners who have helped support make this possible.
Again, free event would not be possible without the support of all of the different people, including the city of Ellsworth, for helping with the venue.
Black Moon, as I mentioned earlier.
We're Wallace Events, our COC Concerts family outside, and Bomb Squad and Artisan.
So lots of different communities helping make this possible, not just our community with the Zao and the musicians, but lots of different people.
So come join us on Saturday.
Thanks, Zoll.
Yeah, thanks, Zoll.
Good to see you.